Bro.
What's up?
Where's the photos you just took of me?
Let me have a look.
I'm busy now.
I'll show you when we're home.
Madam.
Fu Binyan is versatile
and
he's always at the top of his class.
He's the one
who won first prize in the Math Olympiad
last year.
Yibei High
produces talents.
By the way,
this year's freshman representative...
I heard that
he ranked first every year
in all junior high exams.
That's right.
His name is Gu Chenyang.
He's on the next show.
Today,
a new semester begins
and we also embark on
a brand-new chapter of youth.
A brand-new chapter of youth...
Chapter of youth...
Youth means endless possibilities
and boundless responsibilities.
We grow in different surroundings
and weather different storms.
But as long as we chase the bright side,
we will all grow into
who we want to be.
Thank you all.
[Chenyang, relax.]
[Fighting!]
Don't worry, Mom.
I can do it.
Everyone, hurry up.
Okay.
Madam,
please get the costumes ready soon.
Okay.
Do one final sound check.
Gu Chenyang.
I'm looking for you.
Are you ready?
I...
How are you doing?
Gather around and listen up.
The education bureau officials
are here today.
And it's being livestreamed.
Tidy up, everyone,
especially for your name badges.
Make sure they're on straight.
This represents our school.
Understood, teacher.
Don't worry, Ms. Wang.
We won't let Yibei High down.
I trust Zhou Yang.
Go get ready.
Okay.
There we go.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
[Let's thank Fu Binyan]
[from Class 2, Grade 11,]
[for his wonderful show.]
[With beautiful melodies,]
[he shared hopes for the new semester.]
Show them what you've got.
[The spirit of our new students]
[embodies the saying that]
[youth like a rainbow, heart like the sun.]
[Now please welcome our freshman representative,]
[Gu Chenyang from Class 1, Grade 10,]
[to deliver his speech.]
That's him.
Distinguished leaders, teachers,
and dear students,
good morning.
It's my honor to be here
to speak as freshman representative.
I'm from Class 1, Grade 10...
[That's him, Gu Chenyang.]
I'm Gu Chenyang
from Class 1, Grade 10.
[This cold fish.]
[This morning I tried to do the right thing,]
[yet he snapped at me instead of the bad guy.]
[I'm about to be late]
[but he doesn't lift a finger.]
[Cold, heartless,]
[and untrustworthy.]
[Plus he always looks so grumpy.]
[That's Gu Chenyang.]
What happened?
Sorry...
[Thinks he's all that everyday.]
[Just like everyone owes him money.]
[Exactly.]
[I was the first one]
[to step forward.]
[What's more,]
[I was helping him.]
[I know exactly how he is.]
[He never appreciates anyone's help.]
[This kind of people...]
[I just can't understand them.]
Everyone,
Gu Chenyang
draws a lot of attention at school.
So naturally,
people talk about him often,
which just proves...
[He's a tough one.]
[I'm lucky enough not to be his classmate.]
[You can rest easy]
[on that front.]
[Class 1 is the honors class.]
[It's super hard to get into.]
That's right.
Gu Chenyang
has outstanding grades.
He's a
[downer.]
[Forget about him.]
[He ruins my mood.]
Uh...
Madam.
It's just part of the show.
Today,
kids have really
unique ways of thinking.
Very innovative.
It's just part of the show.
Time for the dance!
Be quiet!
Sit down!
So many buttons.
Which one does what?
How would I know?
Stop touching them,
or something will break down.
Lin Qingyuan!
I knew it was you.
If you'd given me a ride,
I wouldn't have been late
and I wouldn't be here.
Watch it!
What are you doing?
Freeze!
Get him!
Pervert!
Freeze!
Out of my way!
Stop!
Freeze!
Out of my way!
Stop!
Don't chase me!
Then don't you run.
The police
are on their way.
Keep running!
I'd like to see how.
Kid,
why don't you
mind your own business?
Stay away! Don't come closer!
I...I warn you!
I know Taekwondo,
Karate,
and Jeet Kune Do.
I don't care what you know.
Believe me.
I'll beat you into the sewer.
Stay away!
Squat down!
That was sick, bro!
Keep running!
Now,
let's see.
You got tough with me?
Come on, do it again!
Are you crazy? Don't move forward!
What if he has one more weapon?
What if he gets away?
Overreaching yourself.
Freeze!
Stop!
Grab him!
Stop running!
Now where are you gonna go?
Think you're so tough?
Kids,
well done.
Young in age, heroic in deed.
Very courageous.
You're from Yibei High, right?
We'll take over from here.
The opening ceremony is today.
Don't be late.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Go on. Get to it.
Okay. Bye.
Serves you right.
Wait, I...
Move.
Seriously?
Secretly filming girls?
Is this yours?
Hey, I'm Lin Qingyuan.
What's your name?
My skateboard broke.
Can you give me a ride?
No back seat.
I can sit up front then.
What's with the act?
Shit. I'm gonna be late.
Good morning.
Hurry up!
The opening ceremony is about to start.
Look, it's Gu Chenyang!
Gu Chenyang!
Long time no see.
You're speaking as the freshman representative today?
Every semester,
we're looking forward to your speech.
We're heading off now.
Goodbye.
Everyone, move faster!
The opening ceremony will begin!
Kid,
the opening ceremony
is about to start.
Hurry inside.
Okay.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Step back!
Late on the very first day of school!
Just one minute.
First day of school,
newbie grace period.
Please let me in.
Not a single second.
Dean Qian says,
no rules, no order.
And you're a freshman?
No school uniform,
no name badge.
I'll make an example of you.
Just you wait.
I...I've got them!
I'll put them on right now.
Gu Chenyang?
Who's that?
Tell me.
What class? Name?
Cover it?
This makes it
far worse.
Write it down.
My name is...
Sun!
Good morning, Dean Qian!
Tricked me again.
Tell me your name.
Who are you?
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Let go!
Who are you?
I'm already late.
Why are you grabbing me?
Are you silly?
Just tell him your name when he asks?
You want to write a self-criticism on the first day?
It makes sense. Thanks.
But...
How do we get inside?
Climb the wall?
Worse if caught?
We won't be caught.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up!
Any slower
and the guards are on us.
Here, hold this for me.
Okay.
Let's go.
Go.
How's that?
Never thought
the first day would be
so exciting.
Stick with me,
and more excitement to come.
Who's there?
"Submarine"!
Which class are you two in?
What "Submarine"?
Let's bolt!
Don't you run!
Stop right there!
[Hello?]
[Alright.]
[I'm on my way.]
[Okay.]
That was quick.
He's gone.
He scared me!
Take a seat.
Relax.
Here, some water.
Thanks.
Why do you
call the dean "Submarine"?
His surname is Qian.
Plus he's always
popping out of nowhere.
You never know
where he'll emerge.
If he's not like a "submarine",
then what is he like?
Fair point.
Stick with me,
and you'll be fine.
After the ceremony,
I'll sneak you back to class.
No one will find out.
Okay.
Li Haoyu?
Milk Tea Senior.
No milk tea today?
Don't mention it.
I just had some milk tea from last night.
which nearly killed me.
Again.
Keep watch for me.
Don't touch anything.
Got it.
Mr. Connections.
Just the usual.
You and I have been through
a crisis together today.
I've got your back around school from now on.
Okay.
I'm Li Haoyu,
lead drummer and captain
of Pulsar Band.
That's awesome.
What's your name?
I'm...
You're also called Gu Chenyang?
No,
this name badge is...
What do you mean by "also"?
Because I know another guy
called Gu Chenyang.
Really?
Sure.
Is it him?
That's him, Gu Chenyang.
[This cold fish.]
[This morning I tried to do the right thing,]
yet he snapped at me instead of the bad guy.
[I'm about to be late]
[but he doesn't lift a finger.]
[Cold, heartless,]
[and untrustworthy.]
[Plus he always looks so grumpy.]
Today, you two
have made yourselves famous.
Give me my things back.
What on earth are you doing?
I knew you were in on it
Li Haoyu.
You are really something.
Unbelievable.
Three years in junior high,
you were known as
the troublemaker.
On the first day of senior high,
you've found your
dynamic duo.
Respect teachers, be friendly to classmates,
and abide by school regulations,
all of which are ignored by you.
Tardiness, climbing over walls, and disrupting order.
You've done it all.
Do you still
respect the school rules?
Dean, we're sorry.
We truly didn't mean it.
We just don't know the equipment.
Next time...
Next time?
Do you realize
how much damage
you've caused to the school?
Dean,
we added a delay to the livestream.
Once the incident happened,
the signal was cut immediately.
The actual impact is limited.
Please don't worry too much.
But the harm done to Gu Chenyang
is undeniable, isn't it?
You two
apologize to him.
We're really sorry, Gu.
Sorry for the trouble.
It's my fault.
Li Haoyu? Li Haoyu!
You got a problem with that?
An apology shows proper attitude,
but punishment still stands.
You two will receive a minor demerit.
Dean, is that really necessary?
Dean,
could you give them
another chance?
Maybe write self-criticisms
and complete campus service
to make amends.
They're freshmen after all.
We could show some leniency.
Zhou Yang,
as the Student Council President,
you shouldn’t always try to be everyone's friend.
Rewards and penalties must be fair.
Besides,
the one in charge of the control room
is from the Arts and Sports Department
of the Student Council, isn't it?
So the Student Council
needs to demonstrate accountability.
Come in.
Dean,
the school nurse said the Arts and Sports Minister
has acute gastroenteritis.
He's already been taken to hospital.
As you see,
there are mitigating circumstances.
As for these two,
they did disrupt
Gu's speech.
How about
making them copy the speech
five times?
Fu Binyan,
you're the Vice President.
What's your opinion?
It doesn't matter.
They didn't interfere with my violin playing anyway.
Maybe we should
follow the President's advice.
Dean,
Jiang Yi isn't here,
but out of the three presidential votes,
we already have two in favour.
In your opinion...
Alright.
Just follow Zhou Yang's advice.
Thank you, Sir.
Make it ten copies
and give it to me tomorrow.
Not enough?
N-no, not at all.
Fu Binyan.
Thanks
for earlier.
I was helping the Arts and Sports Department,
not you.
You still blame me?
Because of the game last semester?
You're overthinking it.
Then why did you stop playing basketball?
Zhou Yang,
since when have you become so talkative?
Let's go.
The Student Council still has work to do.
About what just happened,
I'm sorry.
You freak
look so grumpy.
That's just how he is.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Are you two close?
Not really.
There's no way I'd be close
to someone with such a permanent scowl.
But back there you two…
Alright, alright.
Drop it.
We just met.
Let's add WeChat.
Yeah, good idea.
Come on.
It's okay.
Got it.
Li Haoyu.
Call me Bro Yu.
Okay.
Bro Yu.
See, request sent.
Yep.
I'm Lin Qingyuan.
It's me.
Hey, bro, is this yours?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm Xu Anbo.
Lin Qingyuan.
I know who you are.
The opening ceremony guy.
That's right.
And Li Haoyu.
Mm-hmm.
Who's talking about me?
Help pass these out.
Here, Zhou Yang, hand them around.
Most of you attended Yibei Junior High,
so you should be familiar with the school.
Our school values solid academic foundations,
as well as character and all-round development.
I hope that
while focusing on your studies,
you will also actively develop
your hobbies and interests.
Club Recruitment Day will be this Saturday.
This semester,
the school encourages everyone to join clubs.
Participation in club activities
will count towards your club evaluation scores.
Please choose carefully.
If possible,
I hope you can lead by example
and help the new members
settle into the clubs quickly.
Well done.
[Club activities...]
[We grow in different surroundings]
[and weather different storms.]
[But as long as we chase]
[the bright side,]
[we will all grow into]
[who we want to be.]
This cold fish.
His writing is pretty good.
Finally finished copying.
Grow into who we want to be.
Hey,
toss the ball over here.
Over here!
Perfect shot, bro.